{"data":[{"question":"An accident can happen _____ a split second.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- In a split seconds: an instant; a tiny period of time","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"Mr. Robinson was driving back from Phoenix _____ a windy day when his vehicle collided with a truck.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"The world has changed tremendously _____ a century.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"The last bus leaves _____ 12:25 a.m.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"He was CEO of his own company _____ the age of 28.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- At the age of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"We haven't seen that kind of economic growth _____ a decade.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- - Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for seasons, months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"We assign our employees new tasks _____ a weekly basis.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- On a weekly, monthly, yearly...basic","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"This comes _____ a time when the economy is just beginning to recover.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n-  At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"More people are retiring _____ 62 instead of the traditional 65.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n\n-  At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ At the age of+ year","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"Betty Larson was walking through the park _____ a chilly night last winter when she noticed something moving in the bushes.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for seasons, months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for specific day and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"}]}